Outnumbered. Outgunned. Never out of courage.
Danger Close: The Battle of Long Tan is a war, action,
drama film directed by Kriv Stenders.
Vietnam War, 1966.
Australia and New Zealand send troops to support the United States and
South Vietnamese in their fight against the communist North.
Soldiers are very young men, recruits and volunteers who
have never been involved in a combat.
On August 18th, members of Delta Company will face the true horror of a ruthless
battle among the trees of a rubber plantation called Long Tân.
They are barely a hundred.
The enemy is a human wave ready to destroy them.
Major Harry Smith, played by Travis Fimmel.
Sergeant Bob Buick, played by Luke Bracey.
Private Paul Large, played by Daniel Webber.
Warrant Officer Class 2 Jack Kirby, played by Alexander England.
Captain Morrie Stanley, played by Aaron Glenane.
Private Noel Grimes, played by Nicholas Hamilton.
Danger Close: The Battle of Long Tan is a 2019 Australian war film
about the Battle of Long Tan during the Vietnam War.
It is directed by Kriv Stenders and stars Travis Fimmel.
The film explores themes of vietnam war, based on true story,
1960s, outnumbered, brothers-in-arms relationship.
The tone is emotional.